<databaseChangeLog xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
                   xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                   xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog
                        http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.4.xsd">
    <changeSet id="create_guide" author="anhquynhpham">
        <createTable tableName="tour_guides">
            <column name="id" type="int" autoIncrement="true">
                <constraints primaryKey="true" nullable="false"/>
            </column>
            <column name="name" type="varchar(100)">
                <constraints nullable="false"/>
            </column>
            <column name="experience" type="varchar(50)"/>
            <column name="gender" type="boolean" defaultValueNumeric="false" /> <!--false is male-->
            <column name="price" type="float" />
            <column name="description" type="text"/>
        </createTable>

        <sql dbms="postgresql"
             splitStatements="true"
             stripComments="true">
            insert into tour_guides(name, experience, gender, price, description) values ('Thuan Pham', '7 years', false,
                                    15, 'I was born and raised in Da Nang city. As a a well-experienced Local guide,
                                    I have been guiding tourists around Da Nang and other nearby sites for over 8 years.
                                    I would like to not only tell you about Vietnam’s history in genenally,
                                    about history and culture in particular, but also show you how local people live and
                                    work and help you understand their hopes and dreams.');

            insert into tour_guides(name, experience, gender, price, description) values ('Tam Le', '5 years', false,
                                    10, 'I'm very passionate about guiding tourists traveling to my area of expertise Central Vietnam
                                    or Heritage Road of Central Vietnam including Hoi An ancient town, My Son sanctuary,
                                    Cham Biosphere Reserve, Hue Imperial City, The DMZ, Hamburger Hill and Phong Nha Ke Bang National Park.
                                    Let me be your company for your whole trip to Central Vietnam.');

            insert into tour_guides(name, experience, gender, price, description) values ('Duyen Nguyen', '10 years',
                                    true, 17, 'I have worked as an English speaking guide in Da Nang, Hoi An,
                                    as well as different regions in Vietnam for 10 years.
                                    I love my green country so much and I am proud of its amazing nature,
                                    deep orient culture blended with local traditional customs and long rich history.
                                    Moreover I used to be an English teacher in Hue University of Foreign Languages.
                                    Therefore, my English skills are excellent enabling valued customers to communicate
                                    at a very high level of the issues of history, cultures, architectures, war,...');

            insert into tour_guides(name, experience, gender, price, description) values ('Ha Vu', '1 years', true,
                                    7.5, 'Hello everyone, I am 25 years old.
                                    I graduated from Foreign trade university 2 years ago.
                                    Now I'm a freelancer working as partime tour guide and translator.
                                    I myself have travelled to a lot of places in Vietnam.
                                    I can speak English and Chinese very well.
                                    If you want to travel to Hanoi or any places in Vietnam.
                                    I will be very happy to guide you to visit beautiful places in Vietnam.');

            insert into tour_guides(name, experience, gender, price, description) values ('Huu Duong', '2 years', false,
                                    9, 'Dear my valued clients,
                                    I am a local tour guide in Vietnam. I can guide you through Hoi An ancient town, Da Nang city,
                                    My Son holly land and Hue Imperial City in the middle of Vietnam.
                                    I can arrange an A/C car to pick cruise ship passengers up at the cruise ship entrance
                                    (Chan May, Tien Sa), the airport, train station, hotel lobby, bus stop or road.
                                    I can arrange a golf package during your stay in Da Nang City (Montgomerie Links,
                                    Da Nang Golf Club, Laguna Golf Course, Ba Na Hills club).
                                    I am certified by Vietnam National Administration of Tourism.
                                    I am available for your request and sure to reconfirm your booking request.
                                    I would like to be a bridge of cultural exchange, come with me and share the view.');
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="create_transaction" author="anhquynhpham">
        <createTable tableName="transactions">
            <column name="id" type="int" autoIncrement="true">
                <constraints primaryKey="true" nullable="false"/>
            </column>
            <column name="guide_id" type="int">
                <constraints nullable="false"/>
            </column>
            <column name="plan_id" type="int">
                <constraints nullable="false"/>
            </column>
            <column name="hours" type="float"/>
            <column name="cost" type="float"/>
            <column name="status" type="text"/>
        </createTable>

        <addForeignKeyConstraint baseColumnNames="plan_id"
                                 baseTableName="transactions"
                                 constraintName="plan_fkey"
                                 onDelete="CASCADE"
                                 onUpdate="CASCADE"
                                 referencedColumnNames="id"
                                 referencedTableName="plans"/>

        <addForeignKeyConstraint baseColumnNames="guide_id"
                                 baseTableName="transactions"
                                 constraintName="guide_fkey"
                                 onDelete="CASCADE"
                                 onUpdate="CASCADE"
                                 referencedColumnNames="id"
                                 referencedTableName="tour_guides"/>

        <sql dbms="postgresql"
             splitStatements="true"
             stripComments="true">
            insert into transactions(guide_id, plan_id, hours, cost, status) values (2, 1, 14, 140, 'paid');
            insert into transactions(guide_id, plan_id, hours, cost, status) values (4, 2, 9.5, 71.25, 'unpaid');
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="tag-2.0" author="anhquynhpham">
        <tagDatabase tag="2.0"/>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>